kontain.com 2012-12-09

# Kontain | Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Kontain is committed to protecting your privacy when you use the Kontain Service. The Kontain Privacy Policy describes how Kontain and its affiliates treat personal information when you use Kontain. Its purpose is to inform you of the information we collect about you, how that information is used, whether and to whom we disclose it, and the options you have regarding your personal information.

Please read and understand our Privacy Policy. If you are unable to do so or if you have any questions regarding this or any Kontain Policy, please contact us. Kontain shall have the right to modify this Privacy Policy, which modification shall be effective immediately following Kontain's posting of such change on the Site. We recommend that you check the Site regularly for any such changes. The last updated date is always posted at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Kontain Service following such posting shall be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such modification.

IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THE TERMS SET OUT IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE KONTAIN SERVICE.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

You can use Kontain without having a Kontain account. You can also contact us about a particular video, picture, audio file or other posting without having a Kontain account. Certain other activities on Kontain, such as uploading pictures and videos, posting comments, or creating blogging updates, requires you to have a Kontain account. We ask for some personal information when you create a Kontain account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. A Kontain account allows you to access many of our services that require registration.

_Personally identifiable information._ We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you seek access to certain portions of the Kontain Service, publish or download content, and/or register for our services. This information may be used to fulfill your requests for services, operate, maintain, and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of Kontain, process any flagging activity or correspondence you send to us, communicate with you about your account, support your online activities, respond to your questions, customize your experience and customize the content or features of the Kontain Service. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, physical and e-mail addresses, phone and/or fax numbers, Internet address and type of computer, as well as your preferences and usage patterns. We may also use your personally identifiable information to notify you of changes to Kontain, Terms of Use and/or Privacy Policy. We may record information about your usage, such as when you use Kontain, the other user accounts you visit, the groups and favorites you subscribe to, the contacts with whom you communicate, the media you view, and the frequency and size of data transfers, as well as information you display or click on in Kontain (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page.

_Non-personally identifiable information._ We may also collect aggregated information regarding the use of our service, such as the extent to which certain features are used. Aggregated information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects the scope of our user base, sales, customer patterns and related site information. We use this information to better understand how the Kontain Service is used, and to improve the online experience of our users. This information is not used in a way that will personally identify you. In addition, certain non-personally identifiable information is collected by Kontain and may be used by any third-party advertising providers during the course of your use of the Kontain Service. For example, we may collect aggregated information to determine which advertisements are being viewed, the number of times you have viewed an advertisement (but not your name, address, or other personal information). Such information is used by Kontain and any potential advertising providers to facilitate and monitor the serving of any advertisements Kontain may choose to include.

_Cookies and shared objects._ We may also use cookies and/or shared object to track and understand the traffic on our website. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that our website places onto your computer's hard drive. Cookies identify your computer so that we can recognize you the next time you visit us. We may use cookies and/or shared object to collect and store some information about you, such as the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using, the date and time you access our website and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website. We use this information to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. In the same manner, we may also engage third parties to monitor the usage of, and serve advertising to, the Kontain Service. These third parties may use cookies and Web Beacons (which collect non-personally identifiable information regarding user behavior on our website) to collect such information, which is also used to better understand our users and customize our site for users' particular preferences. You may disable cookies by following directions on your web browser. Disabling cookies also disables web beacons. You should be aware, however, that by disabling cookies and / or shared object you may be unable to access certain services and features of the Kontain Service.

Use of media and public information. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other users when you post media or blog via Kontain. Other information, such as the date you opened your account and the date which you last logged into your account, may also be made public. Remember that all information you post is publicly available, such as a profile picture, you name, gender, relationship status, or other personal details as well as media and blogging updates. Other users may be able to contact you through messages and comments. Any pictures, audio files, videos, comments and other media that you submit to the Kontain Service may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

### Disclosure of Information

We may share aggregated, statistical, non-personally identifiable information about users of Kontain with third-parties, including our distributors, vendors, actual and potential customers and third-parties that offer products or services for use with the Kontain Service. We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

Kontain will not share your personally identifiable information with any third-parties, with the following exceptions:

  1. As necessary to third parties who perform services for us in operating and marketing the Kontain Service, including, but not limited to, the monitoring of user behavior on our website and the processing of payments for any products or services. 
  2. We may be obliged or deem it necessary or appropriate to disclose your information in response to legal process such as a court order or subpoena; to prevent or combat fraud; as required by federal or state law; enforcement of our Terms of Use; and protection of the rights, property or safety of Kontain, our users, our employees or our affiliates' employees, or others. 
  3. We may disclose your information in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of our company and to parents, subsidiaries or affiliates of Kontain LLC. 

Kontain's Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, any advertisers or other web sites. Users or advertisers may post information which will contain links to third-party websites. These other sites have their own privacy policies and you should review those policies before following those links. Kontain does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks or other web sites without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

### Security

Kontain is committed to taking appropriate measures to protect your privacy against unauthorized disclosures. The Kontain Service uses a variety of secure techniques designed to protect your information. While we have implemented safeguards, you should be aware that Internet security technology rapidly changes. As such, we cannot guarantee that the safeguards we employ today can protect your personal information from the threats of tomorrow, or that our security measures are failsafe and not subject to circumvention or unauthorized intrusion. You should also be aware that, despite our best efforts, factors beyond our control may result in disclosure of data.

### Young Children

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13. To best protect your child's privacy, we suggest that you carefully supervise your child's access to the Internet and our website. For more information on how to protect your child's privacy, you can visit the Federal Trade Commission's Kidzprivacy page, accessible via www.ftc.gov.

### Notice for Users Outside of the United States

You should be aware that the United States and other countries have not harmonized their privacy regulations. This Privacy Policy is written to satisfy United States regulations. Your country may have different standards for privacy and therefore we suggest you research those if you intend to use the Kontain Service from outside of the United States. By using the Kontain Service, you agree to the level of privacy protection set out in our Privacy Policy.

### More Information

For questions concerning Kontain or your account, please contact us via email, or write to us at:

Kontain

Go on and Kontain your life,  
**Kontain's friendly legal team**

Last updated October 1, 2008
